desihome.info 2014-06-25

# DesiHome.Info - Privacy Policy

DesiHome cares about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting DesiHome.Info you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

  * We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out for saving your gaming scores, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.
  * We use cookies with minimal information in them. 
  * We use Google Analytics, which is covered by [Google Privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html)
  * We allow you to contact other members via profile pages, but no private information is sent unless you want them to see. (you can choose not receive any communication from anyone.)

**In details**

  1. **What does** **DesiHome** **Privacy Policy cover?**  
On registration we collect your name, email, date of birth and biographic information (optional). The personal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in DesiHome Games you must complete a registration form (Guests also allowed to play, but scores are not saved for Guests). As part of registration form, we require your email address.
  2. **Cookies  
**Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computerâ€™s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in DesiHome server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
  3. **Third-party Advertisement**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 
  4. **Membership Validity**  
We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended.   

Last modified: 10th August 2012
